yo yo for boxes pandas are here anyone
periscope yeah right they're here oh
that's smaller than you imagined right
that's a thousand pandas get a knife
from macro fact they are exclusive not
exclusive yet
good good tight tight time hi-yah just
cross out aunty so yeah yeah yeah Andy
I'm got Eddie we got pandas oh yeah
because pandas are going on Amazon you
guys know about safety that's in two
boxes I'm not gonna tell you guys but
loop is who knew calibration of DSP with
the DSP we got to use the DSP for DSP
guys all right all right
so macro fab is our manufacturing part
and one of our manufacturing partners
for pandas one of our many occupiers
exclusive we're getting a parent express
to be the exclusive IRL distributors but
unless yes let's open a box alright if
they're not good we're gonna put now
live on periscope to react the DSP knows
outraged so fine line yeah no it's good
oh one is good oh this is a good panda
it's a great man oh man wait let's plug
it in its use with a great these are
nice it good job macro found coming
through
yeah no we had some quality issues but
it looks like we've worked through them
let's plug this pandan to make sure it
works oh yeah
nice nice nice look at that panda dude
and there's literally you see all these
boxes just really
so we're gonna put them through our
rigorous QA procedure going back to the
manufacturer that's what we're gonna do
when they don't work the foam on the
side they don't work they go back to the
manufacturer wait put that one to take
that one and put it in the box you can
put it back put it back in no no no
discount we don't ship anything bad
quality we're going downstairs we're
gonna take these pandas into QA why did
they how did somebody put it you know
what 99% of them look good no no no the
first ones were made in-house yeah but
all these ones have been made by an
acrobat what is a panda a panda the
nicest universal car interface ever and
you can buy one right now in shop comic
valet guy you can even get one of these
you want to say hi to the periscope
people this is Chris love so newest
comment I employee and we're taking four
panels I asked absolutely
Chris the jar right yes yeah Chris is a
jar yeah so no there's no flex on pandas
guys but yeah that's Chris and these are
pants
so we're gonna box all of these yeah
pandas are small but wait yeah we're
gonna unbox oh I got some bags we're
gonna unbox and test all of these pandas
or you're planning on expanding what do
you mean by expanding Chris is working
on JavaScript he's working on Cabana
panda Jaya these nice big all of this
stuff to truly make Panda a five-star
experience as a nice bag to truly make
Panda a five-star experience because
guys
pandas are going to Amazon you all know
it that's why they have real UPC's that
look good
actually it's a GTI M GTI yeah maybe
we'll just test this box we'll see we'll
see at least look at all the box if not
a single one of them fail well yeah you
gotta look at all the boxes why is panda
J is so important because javascript is
the future you guys yeah we're gonna
code the new open pilot in we're gonna
move from Python to JavaScript
JavaScript OVA pilot drive my car dot
today we own the domain
applications with the panda so if you
have a specific car and you can unlock
some fancy feature and with the cars
electronics you can use panda je s in
order to write a simple script or ship
it in an application on the web or on
mobile apps or on your desktop to unlock
your car against all your features get
everything you can out of your car with
kind of je s good pitch ya know
javascript is a hugely growing language
um you know I I'm a Python guy but um
yeah for everybody's like making apps
today using react and stuff we really
want panda to just be the most
supportive best car to face ever and
also we want Schiffer to use passage is
what about those know how to code you
can use Java scripts great language you
can also use Python we have a Python
library for Panda an open pilot we have
a C++ library for panda called boardy
you can use that we're moving to a
bigger office
no with there's a lot more room and
there are like three rooms in this house
you guys have never seen why would you
buy a white panda instead of a gray one
half the price comes with Wi-Fi can you
make a pigeon antenna with a shorter
cable we don't put the cables on the
antennas guys when's the house gonna be
full I think we can fit at least five
more people in this house
there are literally three rooms you guys
have never seen yeah well they've never
seen that room no and they never really
seen this room yeah and they've never
seen the tiny room where Willem used to
live all rights go
yeah good this issue is now been fixed
the boxis you can you believe that I
mean that's like someone builds these
how would they know what I can move out
there's my room as well um builds these
yeah I understand yeah boxes are good
well these all look good there's no glue
on they look like a good product yeah
oh you have seen the internal okay you
guys have seen that room though there's
still two engines you know like you see
these look good you know we want to ship
you guys only the best stuff if the
antennas not directly above the camera
how could it be so accurate calibration
bros yeah it's live in the closet no no
no no we're trying to hire a recruiter
so they're crude oil be joining they've
in our office
how good is macro Fair's been a few
hiccups recently and getting any
manufacturing that's ok that's hard
we've been happy yeah and they're way
better than like you know these local
board houses in oh oh yeah price-wise
price-wise that's right yeah we're gonna
quote from someone in like San Jose yeah
like insane they're not transparent
about what's going on that comes great
because they show you literally what
you're paying for the part don't maybe
the cost they may be your main boards
and labor we will show them the circuit
how grand palace yeah these are from our
other guys working with our github Sarah
come home with a set of samples we're
working on it
no macro fats actually been great like
you see we get those pandas just all
like that in the box from macro fine
yeah we sent them a procedure and a
laptop and they program oh oh you saw
they want to USB kina getting one
another I wasn't only one USB but we
know so it's made our life it's made our
life a lot easier yeah we used to play
look good cool and your mate and testing
CTF days yeah a lot of people work here
man factory injected midnight black yo
you want ejection welded Aeons no it's
not happy
no they're not you can't make them on
other than Jackson long we're big fans
of 3d printing here guys by the way yeah
we're looking if anybody knows we're
looking for 2001 plus 3 TC like has got
a truck yeah
how much is macro crap nu du shell
nothing nothing Vidya was a good deal we
made a good deal with manufacturing
families we tweeted about them once yeah
look put it this way when they get us
the remaining of the Panda order and
their QC great we'll have great things
to say about Mack around yeah yeah
definitely some again this is our first
big shipment yeah so we're excited oh no
you can't send in a phone and have it
converted to a neon I don't want to I
want to thousand why not upgrade from
the three T to the five T because the
five T is too extensive five hundred
dollars and we don't make profit anymore
and you guys know that I'm a capitalist
greedy bastard and love profit am i we
can't exist without profit right like
someone's got to pay for all this guys
you think Ratan San Francisco's cheap
why can't we use the new one pluses
because you can't buy them cheap and in
quantities custom hardware Eon Wow hey
you know is the next Aeon r1 no no no no
no the Aeons will always be Beyonc
if you bought an e on it will never
change its name one day
it's damaged at all in it then you put
it in the bag look at like the box
tearing like it's something well this is
a new cue season they sent us more what
they need foam on each layer like it's
not that big a deal because we have
extra boxes yeah that's like yeah well
if the only problem is a lot of them put
foam on each will the next one be called
env2 maybe I don't know guys who said
there is the next one females for life
yeah yeah I mean if this is shipping
damage and it's like honestly it's like
it's like boxes get them though I just
don't care what I do for box we get down
they cost me nothing we have equipment
boxes yeah but does not because like one
day we want them to send and I think if
every one of these passes qce except for
the box
can we won't even have to open the other
boxes okay what did Eddie do before come
on you want to tell them oh I worked in
New York for a year now actually 360 how
many three 265 but I worked there for
one year so I didn't have to pay them
back for my moving expenses and it was a
leap year
so I like saved a nice oh we do have
something very serious to ask miss go
peace guys when Pam was going Amazon who
right now honestly would give panda a
five-star review stay you should get a
ponytail that doesn't okay yeah no guys
like we're really working on panda
quality we're working on making the best
libraries yeah and once it does go in
Amazon we really would appreciate only
if you feel that way about the product
if you don't feel like the Panda
deserves a five-star review don't leave
don't leave marina but don't don't leave
a five-star review if you don't really
believe it's a five-star product um
don't you need to be a buyer only
amazon.com
first I don't know like you have to have
bought the product well I mean you guys
all did buy the prod like don't leave a
five star review if you don't own a pan
that have used it it is way better than
the other candidate offenses like we I
think if the shipper pairing is now good
and we have panel Jas launched I think
this is very clearly because you know
reviews a super board on Amazon how much
support in Europe does the whole kind of
platform have you guys pass ridiculous
data protection laws so less talk to God
love your covenants really we're focused
on US Canada Mexico also your import
taxes we're big fans of NAFTA here yeah
yeah yeah global free trade global
America free trade that's right what
user demonstrate that case is all look
good yeah any that are marginal there's
one well they have prime shipping
absolutely that's a good print yeah we
love Amazon nice she's all about working
consciously driving the left I don't
know ma'am I've never tested every we
leave we only tested on the right by the
boxes okay just some of them can you
seen from the outside no it's just like
doesn't fold nice okay maybe something
else
okay shipping is already super fast you
know guys but we got to get a non-prime
this Tesla going down
no Tesla's doing super well 5 star if
supports most el maps okay well we'll
make sure we what we want to do we both
are is one el maps but with most couple
with with cars and with El maps we're
gonna make a list of ones that are
supportive make a better app than
Scheffer yeah maybe maybe we should make
it yeah
put the El map features in shipper well
but we're gonna take select features
that he'll maps will provide you really
shipper and shipper is too we have a
looking manager drive we have a look
into the other negotiation stuff no well
so although bought is a different thing
negotiation no but like you know some of
the people are saying it like makes the
check engine light turn out in their car
you gotta figure out what that is before
you go Amazon yeah certainly if you have
a car where the pan is please ping me in
our slack and coming to her shipper
panda channels and feedback yeah yeah if
you're having if you're having a problem
with with like torque on your car we
want to know will rent your car and make
it better
is this a Kickstarter video this is not
a Kickstarter video okay
we considered Kickstarter
expenses and also like we have money to
layout for product we don't need to
raise money from the crowd you guys know
I've talked about on periscope a few
times we did raise a new funding round
recently we have we have too much money
too much - give so much back that's fine
I reaction look we actually raised I'm
very happy with our race and the fact
that we managed to do it without giving
up the boards yeah if you order an e on
today we will ship it you tomorrow for
equity what do you mean for equity how
do you start a self-driving car
companies don't start a company only
this year am I happy I started a company
for the first three years I was not yeah
yeah because the only reason I'm happy
now but I started the company is because
we're doing well products exactly like
and you don't we're buying more products
and the products are getting better and
you know the industry is shaping up kind
of exactly how I thought it was yeah
like what like no I took two years ago I
told you that in two years
wham-o is not going to be driving
everybody around in all the cities with
an easy app and sure enough I think
stuff is just not human level yet maybe
it is super hard and you know the way
that you do it is not with like 100 cars
in your fleet it's like we're like
Tesla's different we have way more cars
than way mo now wait last year it was
close before we were selling Eon now
it's not even close we probably want to
double as many cars is waiting for us
when Moe's gonna get 20,000 cars win in
two years we passed them these you
realize were actually in second place
right that's right Oh 20 2000
how many you're driving with comma five
hundreds yeah it'll be thousands by the
end of the year cool guys well thank you
joining ya pandas so all the pandas that
you get now from us will be the new
style injection-molded opens off the
website the old one I think there's one
picture of it laughter we can delete
that picture but all the pandas that
ship now are injection molds $99 comes
in cute little box
yep they all ship we ship to Canada
absolutely yeah we ship all over the
world thanks to DHL we do ship all over
the world but I think Amazon I think
we're only doing u.s. Amazon
I like items are very restrictive I
don't know if we will ship to other
countries hopefully we can support you
in the UK suit I mean you can certainly
buy a panda that you okay yeah you get
rid of your ridiculous data protection
laws guys oh come on what oh let me be
GDP or compliant um some European
regulator is watching me right now
seizing all my orders and customs not
allowed to say bad things about the EU
not saying bad things about the EU just
the GDP are amazon.ca yeah thanks bro
that was on CA I don't know it's like if
it's like one click and I can click like
Canada new model will require Maps no
but it'll be helped with maps if we want
to get to like the insanely high levels
of quality we want you know like look at
if Tesla had to have maps like the
autopilot crash wouldn't happened not
blaming Tesla blaming the drivers not
paying attention pay attention guys
but um yeah yeah you can't you can't
rely on maps you can't rely on like you
need in order to get safety there's just
a huge mixture of things yeah the new
model for you don't write the new
European law just says to encrypt the
password and make anonymous public
information we do both of those things
but I don't know man
some people like edit detailed
instructions to get started Google
update on website for getting new UI
fullscreen but only full screen do we
shut the screen shift full screen yeah
mapping with that great pant I know I
looked at one of your routes America
first guys and I don't mean like America
first like a combative way I just live
in America it's easy for me you know a
born in America I love America but yeah
cool
thanks for joining fire Panda and make
sure when we're on Amazon you leave that
five-star view
we love five star reviews.i by